CHRISTINA XAMIN

CONTACT

cxamin@gmail.com



(416)-523-3132



www.christinaxamin.com

2232 Wuthering Heights Way Oakville, ON, Canada L6M 0A3

SKILLS

- Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite
- Confident working with both Macs and PCs, as well as their accompanying software (Microsoft Office, iWork, etc.)
- Understanding of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Excels in use of social media outlets (including Twitter, Instagram, Facebook, YouTube. Pinterest and Tumblr)
- Ability to work in a team with a wide range of people
- Able to make decisions and work through problems
- Manages time effectively
- Easily adapts to new situations
- Presents ideas and opinions in an open and unbiased way

CERTIFICATIONS

CPR Level C + AED

Ambitious designer with 4+ years experience in a professional design environment. Currently working towards a Bachelor of Interaction Design degree. Highly proficient in graphic design. video editing and web design software. Background in visual and creative arts using both traditional and digital elements.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Interaction Design Sheridan College

September 2014- Present

Visual and Creative Arts Advanced Diploma Sheridan College

January 2012 - May 2014

EXPERIENCE

INTERACTIVE AND TECHNICAL MEDIA WRITER INTERN Rapid7, Toronto, ON

May 2017- September 2017

- Guided users through UI by contributing to company's software help documentation
- Migrated content to a new platform and organized information to reduce outdated content
- · Collaborated with multiple teams to create documents that outlined in-product features

GRAPHIC DESIGNER (CONTRACT) AFL Canada, Toronto, ON

November 2013- March 2014, November 2016- January 2017

- Designed Men and Women's International Cup jerseys for AFL International Cup 2014 and 2017
- Created design mockups catered towards clients needs

GRAPHIC DESIGN ASSISTANT (CONTRACT) Oakville Public Library, Oakville, ON

May 2016- August 2016

- Produced various promotional material for print, web and environmental applications
- · Maintained a graphic consistency by adhering to the library's visual identity and AODA compliancy
- Provided branding and graphic support for the 2016 TD Summer Reading Program